Okay, thank you very much.
Thank you for having me, thank you for coming to this session.
Thank you for finding time in your very, very busy schedules
to actually listen to the concept of Problem-Based Learning.
PBL is actually very close to my heart.
Actually, before I go there,
I want to say a few words about myself.
So my name is Pawel M. Kindler.
I'm currently a visiting research fellow here at NTNU,
Professor Mao has been a wonderful host.
but my home base is in the Department of
Cellular and Physiological Sciences
at the undergraduate program at the
University of British Columbia in Vancouver.
I'm a reproductive endocrinologist by training,
but I have a very very deep interest
in medical education and for the past ten years or so,
the focus of my research has been
problem-based learning primarily.
As I mentioned earlier, PBL is very
close to my heart,
I've been a PBL tourer for the past 12 years.
I'm also a member of a very small group of facility,
maybe there are between four or five of us
responsible for training new PBL tutors.
As I said, my current research interests are focused on PBL and so
I'm really happy and grateful to you that there seems to be quite a bit of interest
around problem-based learning. As Professor Mao said,
I don't really speak Chinese but
I understand that she mentioned we'll have
a more interactive workshop during the
conference on May 6
this is going to be just a bit of didactic introduction
to the whole concept of Problem-Based Learning,
and so I'll end up talking, you know
you know which always makes me feel a bit uncomfortable because PBL
is all about interactions
it's a very interactive pedagogy
and here I am giving a lecture which sort goes against the principles of PBL
But I think there's no way to avoid this
we need to have a brief session just
covering the basic concepts of PBL.
I'd like to start with a bit of a definition
of problem-based learning.
There are many definitions in the literature, some of
them are difficult to understand
This one is one that I like, it's by Matthew Grief
from National University of Singapore
and what he says is that
PBL is a derivative of of the
constructivist theory aimed at enhancing
and optimizing the educational outcomes
of learner-centered collaborative contextual
integrated, self-directed, and reflective learning.
Of course, no one is expected to memorize this definition,
but I think it's important to start with it,
because it's one indication that
we will be talking about a comprehensive pedagogy.
PBA is not just about to giving our students problems,
of course this also affects
those who lecture in front of large classes
and trying to make sure that our lectures are
as interactive as possible, and of course
we use all sorts of things including problems.
We give our students problems, the expectation is that they discuss those problems in small groups
and then of course, talking a bit about
this whole class forum
This is a very effective way to engage students
students but it has nothing to do
with problem-based learning.
There's more to PBL than just giving
students problems to think about and so
this is what we will discuss for most of this session.
So I translated this theoretical concept, or definition
into a language that reflects practice.
And so, we can say that PBL is a small group-based, student-centered, highly interactive pedagogy
in which learners construct new
ideas based upon their existing knowledge
that's a reference as I'm
sure you know,
to the constructivist theory of learning
and which is designed to help students become
self-directed learners. This is one of the ultimate goals.
Whether it's medicine, engineering or any other field, young people these days work in teams,
it's extremely important,
and they are also expected to be independent
and this is one of the concepts that
PBL is supposed to provide our students with.
They're supposed to learn
how to become self-directed learners.
So a bit of history,
my entire experience with PBA has been
in field of medical education
but this is where PBL was introduced for the first time.
Almost fifty years ago, all the way back in 1969,
some of you were not even born back then.
That was at McMaster University at Hamilton, Ontario, Canada.
This pedagogy has been around for quite some time.
It's one of very few pedagogues that were
introduced in 1960's that have not only survived
but are becoming more and more popular.
And so PBL has spread widely across
continents
First in Canada, then the US and Europe.
As many of you know,
Lebanon was one of the centers of PBL,
Australia and Asia as well.
It has gained a very wide acceptance
beyond just medicine and the sciences.
Here are just some of the examples of
of the areas where
PBL has been introduced and has been used for years.
Education, engineering, psychology, and
so on.
Even in school learning
in the States and in Europe in the Netherlands,
there have been attempts to introduce PBR even in kindergarten.
So the next interesting point I would like to make
is that going back to medical education
once again, which I'm most familiar with,
is that there probably as many versions of PBL
as there are medical schools that use it.
Each medical school uses a slightly different version.
That corresponds to the environment and lack of expectations and requirements.
However, and this is what I
will spend most of the time talking about
the principles of PBL are always the same.
There are some key aspects of PBL
that have to be introduced
if we really want to refer to what
we are doing as problem-based learning.
So what are those principles of PBL
Well, first of all, PBL always involves the use of cases,
in medicine, it's typically cases based on real patients.
We want medical students to begin to think like doctors
from early stages of their training.
The cases are typically based on real medical cases.
So the patients that are introduced
in those cases are actually real patients.
The second requirement is that students
collaborate in small groups.
There's no way to avoid this.
This is really a small group-based category.
The size of the groups will vary typically between 5 and 12.
There has been quite a bit of research
indicating that once you go beyond eight,
the interactions may become a challenge
because the more the people there are,
the more difficult it is for everyone to be
engaged and that's one of the principles of PBL.
Everyone in the group participates.
So what is the third principle of PBL?
Well, that learning is facilitated by a trained tutor.
Every school that offers PBL
provides actual tutors with training.
At UBC, that training only lasts two mornings,
so together it's eight hours of training.
But if someone wants to become a PBL tutor,
they have graduate from that training program.
Otherwise they are not allowed
to serve as tutors.
The next important point is that the
curriculum includes a limited number of lectures
and this is often controversial
this is one of those components of PBL that are often very difficult to implement.
But it is very closely linked to the
last principle, which is that
the curriculum provides sufficient time for self-study.
So the message here is that you can't just add PBL to the existing to curriculum and expect the
students to really take full advantage of it.
So this is not a pedagogy that is
introduced to make students even busier,
because it is medical students or students at NTNU, wherever area they are,
they're all very busy, and typically they don't really have time in their schedules to add something
as time demanding and time-consuming as program-based learning.
And so there has to be a decision made at the level of the university
or at the level of the college
or at the level of the department,
that, ok, we want to introduce PBL,
how do we go about
making room for it in our curriculum?
That conversation has to take part during this process.
By the way, I could leave few minutes at the end of this session for questions, but if you have any questions
don't hesitate to ask us as we sort
of cover all these different topics.
So let me just quickly summarize what
happens during this process
So small groups of learners are
presented with carefully designed-
I'll talk a bit more about this a few minutes-
and progressively released problems
So PBL students don't really get a problem,
they're not introduced to the whole problem right at the beginning,
they are introduced to problem gradually.
So initially, they receive some
introductory information about the case
They talk about it, as I'll mention in a second,
and then when they decide that they're ready for more, they receive more information.
The problems are released to the students progressively.
The group then discusses the case and generates initial explanations
for the underlying processes,
principles, and mechanisms.
and it doesn't matter if it's medicine,
engineering, or education,
the way PBL works is very very similar
regardless of the area.
And then through collaborations in small groups, learners build up on their prior knowledge to
to construct the theory to explain the problem.
And that's a reference to the
constructivist theory of learning.
The constructivist theory of learning assumes that we learn by utilizing our existing knowledge
and that learning is a social process, social activity,
hence, small groups.
Questions that arise during
this initial discussion events are then
are then formulated into what we refer to as "learning issues."
affect us and learning issues ok and he
just 11 issue is that students to
and basically use them for
subsequent individual self directed learning.
So this is when the students are
responsible for finding resources,
basically trying to explore, discover, and learn the concepts captured by those learning issues
****
of them but this
is the time when students walking down
the entire case of our medical school
students have progress about one day
because we have our complete sessions
our Mondays Wednesdays and Fridays 8 to
10 in the morning and sell sell sell
another case has to his credit of time
at the same time of course they're busy
with other aspects of their curriculum
that we have time and again and I'm
gonna make reference to the same later
they soon became our curriculum there is
actual time divers battles that is
reserved for self-study you honestly
expect our students to read it
job and then be able to find those
resources be a military tool and instead
of you but I understand this concept
given time you know we can't assume that
they did as well as their banner their
homework and I and Sauvignon Blanc at
night and extremely tired they would say
gee so there's two ppl and I need to
still do my money just isn't going to
work if you if this is how how how PPO's
into is introduced that has since come
back and this information that the heads
up just messaged is discussed ok this
assumption is that all students dealing
with them slightly different
understanding of the problem slide who
dis an understanding of the mechanism
that they were supposed to learn and
said they have a conversation about
scientifically
again in our case on Wednesday or that
which is the second to tie all the other
week half of that the Toronto is spent
on that combat discussion among the
students so they all talk about this
when they've learned what to type of
information to his family while they
sing throughout the event while they
think you know them so that they are
there might be something
problems they've read it is that they
don't understand you know and and that's
that's a very very interactive
conversation that students are having
again during that first half of the
second of the second tutorial and then
very very important again all these
discussions are facilitated by a train
tutor okay and and this is never going
to do it that's why we provide to us
with training so let's talk about cases
for just a minute or two to see that's
why are they so keep principles which
case it's a good enough to generate
we're not talking about just you know a
brief paragraph that students will let
up to easy they just let talking very
often fairly complex somalia's ok but
they must be relevant they must be less
hectic and then must be interesting as I
got a one of the challenges that we have
you know me you know I'm side written
three cases in in in injuring my my
career as a people to it's it's a very
very challenging thing to do
takes lots of time ok but it's better to
know his parents I'm not interesting are
not relevant ones soon as I'm not going
to the end
gauge
with the have two aspects to this level
of prior knowledge you know if if if if
if you tell us to dance 2222 consider a
case that there would be really had no
idea that was completely you know and we
will everything be cases bang you to
them this is going to be very difficult
to generate conversation especially
initially be so so sad thoughts that
case has to attract students who have a
it has to be within a way that triggers
group discussion this is what it's all
about and tested generate desired any
issues such as a two-year going to help
students to you know to wind down stairs
there's desired length at the taste good
with in case really provide students
with other direction too many and of
course encourage and support
self-directed learning to has to be done
in this case has to generate blemishes
that students will be excited about
exploring on the edges a quick drink
piss off and developed by teams
consisting of a faculty member with a
wide range of wedding dress
expertise and so for example medical
education often these teams are composed
of clinicians and basic scientists
because really we often used as cases to
you know to introduce two students other
basic science mechanisms but in a
clinical context and saigon you can
learn all you can eat I can get this
this applies to any discipline
engineering education and so on
you know i the voting of cases is that
thing work
to make severely rest of students and
teachers in PBS because they've been
very very different than normal said on
Monday Dr interactions the students
1,100 increasing responsibility and
because they have to be self-regulated
learners right that went to be periods
of time went on they will be responsible
for other lending but at the same time
they'll have to treat culturally in most
cases greater motivation for that they
had greater ownership of learning
because they believe they know they will
be ready Monday and so so so so
hopefully you know this will generate
any of this no excitement among the
students for talking to you that this is
this is really did the Q 44 any
right that's five years he will do not
engage directly in information transfer
and so we do have textured joined the
times you will never see me doing this
during any of my my Pediatr toys and and
you know I gotta do this for 30 years
I've never give another election ppl to
my students it's not this this isn't
yeah they're not trying to impede your
forgiving righteous and you're not
supposed to do this right thoughts are
so that's that's a that's a very very
important point thanks to its a
challenge for two hours again this is
one of the reasons why we provide them
with training because we are used to
teaching about dr. so they'd acting so
they don't they don't have sunny and
include your not suddenly you I'm not
expected you are not allowed to do that
to provide direct answers so sorry
students we often be tempted to ask you
to help them you can have them but you
know they were used to facilitate this
process will not providing students with
their time since it's their
responsibility to come out to come out
with the census service facilities to
build to guide students in
problem-solving right this is how this
is and we'll talk more about this this
is about to see two minutes and provide
feedback and assessment again a very
difficult thing to do something that
many of us I'm not used to do it
an active participant in without being
the source of information
this primary venice is a very important
computers are at least great period
tunes of those experts on the subject
matter you have to know the subject
matter you know if you want to be a
tutor in PDF if you don't have subject
expertise is going to be very difficult
but they're also trained
effective facilitation of student
learning we receptive this through this
period he a sexual congress so in other
words and then there's many studies in
deep in Europe literature showing that
students used language that is used by
the students and suddenly be willing to
give you the latest news on religious
views by this to you know they they will
try to think like their students they
will become part of the process and this
is when students will accept them as as
as as as to who scored 21 who comes with
with the process so what else needs
service certainly assist coaches and
managers say goodbye now thanks to the
the the workshop in May will be all bad
this year or what what what can we do
when we experienced problems during this
process we're talking about small groups
that are several small groups consisting
of very smart young people and you know
this leads to concepts
frequently and so what are those
countries with and what should you
expect as a putative and how what
strategies can you employees to address
this conference and as asset because
again dispute as we provide both
feedback and we assess students so let's
listen to the Citizen Service innovating
through positive learning environment
can we talk about
importance that saved positive learning
environment
students has to Syria safe have to feel
comfortable nice to say I don't know for
many students it's a very difficult to
say this is particularly true orphan
drugs and medical students who ran
through this extremely competitive
process where delivered to medical
school raised here in Thailand
lieutenant in the USA Europe it's the
same all over the place as we all know
you know the party's over black students
end up in medical schools and so you
know they assume that they and their
guns are from Dave on there are ready to
be ductus well in people on the go
quickly realized the best not the case
and said he has to create the studios we
have to create an environment where
there are still waiting to acknowledge
this and you know because because that's
bob is going to be rainy day really
well one of the reasons that they are
really engage actively in in in the
process by saying by admitting to
themselves after they pierce my goodness
I don't want this I don't really
understand it or not this is I just know
I start of this concept in a completely
different way so this is how it goes
you know you know fantastic now under
you know there has to be this kind of
conversation during during during people
and hanging over for this to happen as a
tutor you have to make sure that's that
students feel safe 27 cents and again
many of them I'm not used to saying that
as a percentage of them have to ensure
that students are involved in active
learning n English process on a lot of
the assumptions of PDA is that everyone
participates ok and so so so as as a
similarly often asked Bruce types of
questions with someone who hasn't spoken
much to their place summarizes the key
points for the blue
ways to engage and again we'll talk more
about us and our workshop on your night
at their home ways to engage students
school hasn't really pass it but
dissipated in the process this is a lot
of them and so say around seven st. John
you haven't really set a record today
know what's going on I want you to
on says this single problem that that
you know you know are considered every
single problem in the case you know that
drip mother went very well so this is
this is a much better way of informing
or elvis other students know that is it
today we've noticed that about how
participating at the expected level and
hey you know it's time it's time to
begin to to get involved as a coach you
prayed students know it's our students
laughed then that barring that that of a
disservice correct their last 22 to
assume that what they've learned is is
quite well that's not the case and as I
get to know its responsibility to really
keep an eye on this and when students
begin to say things that are not correct
well you have to you have to as a tutor
is this possibility to add to the
address as a radar says a coach assist
students developed and developing
deductive reasoning skills and so they
sang sang the song just a few
example two of two types of questions
that says the two of you may want to ask
him in a situation like this where I go
again one of my students the same things
thats maybe I'm not necessarily have the
highest quality could you explain your
reasoning behind that assets that are
saying I hope this doesn't make sense
what you just said let's have some more
sense you know will save around the
reasoning behind you know could you tell
us why you think this is this is this is
this is sort of the way this particular
thing or a college professor hypothesis
I just sure examples are indicating to
the grid that as a deficit as a as a as
a as a two-year limit then we're going
to be concerned about the quality of
some of the some of the concepts tough
day at thirty days
contribute an event you know it can be a
medicine that you can be in any other
field education engineering and so on
then we serve as a model for records
management group dynamics here on
Craig's List identified in South promise
I gotta go talk more about this in a
more interactive workshop laptop and a
small test of SMS students assuming you
mean as human beings in general
room typically have difficulty
addressing problems while addressing
conflict and of course there's some and
then you know part of my night session
in May ready to talk about some of the
pieces so he says that's the level of
myself comparing the types of problems
that that PDA group's experience in Asia
and in in in Canada we did a study
comparing Hong Kong University of Hong
Kong and Andy BC and new media
to the types of problems that students
experience during the two-time US and
came up with some some interesting some
interesting information back to bed time
but again you know it's important for us
to develop a culture we will have a grid
where certain swear you know pay
attention to her to process and he died
problems it does show since there's
conflict day rose they rarely fear that
it still is possibility to address we
had a tendency to leave to pretend that
everything is fine that's done no
problems develop under System Texas tell
us that they can actually have a very
very but ran into an impact on the
quality of learning and so they have to
be there has to be addressed I will rise
to help process may get the right now
instead of saying well you know
this way this gripping Center after you
may want to affect the ground rules this
is something I haven't really talked
about talked about but let him being a
min Kevia typically he's been students
meet the very very first for the very
first time we spent about five minutes
talking about ground rules you know the
expectations
record is supposed to happen during bad
during the during these sessions you
know it's it's it's it's sort of very
often very simple things you know be on
time you know this is a very special and
are in the context of professional
school medical school law
you know what I wrote and engineering
you know being on time I mean you know
if if it started with professional
behavior idea on time and so that's a
very very very they say that's very
important thanks to the paint to pay
attention to make sure that time that
you participated in November going
through those groups make sure that he
participates you know in the industry
into terrorist make sure that's you
dance over participate you know may be
wrong but I'm glad step years and under
that doesn't there let's say you know
you this year + 77 students may share
that sooner you you monitor do a you and
your you participate in the process a
lot of her life in this group of unknown
group can really have a chance to do to
participate are you can say I have known
as the discussions haven't been there
soccer's to do you think that this is a
problem what can we do to improve it
right and so so you know you know you
notice that something is wrong and you
and you really
invited the group again to come up with
some action so it was very important
point about do any of the two is that
developed the torch really involved in
this process we stopped by modeling the
the process right to meet you see you
know typically you know was stabbed her
the group of students remain very little
about this process and so you have to
you have to serve as a model through to
the metamodel certain behaviors
yesterday another set of 10 cents
uncertain
basins contribute to the process says
that as a tutor was very much involved
in the US because then students have to
learn from you let us prepare rate to
engage in in this process then until I
assumed would be coming with us tomorrow
mom coaching you concentrate more on
making sure that you know I and everyone
is contributing that that's you know
that no more
and there's no conflict in the grip and
ten you know and and again you your your
your your involvement becomes much much
less direct and final was sort of the
fair you know modest a very modest a
good time to turn us into something here
in in our medical problem is when I
don't have to say I just sit there and I
was left my grip their job because
battle because not Glendale not this
process inside out and so it is very
important to remember that the beam
dynamics of ppl and they are going to be
very very different than the men
dynamics of ppl after students have had
the opportunity to do it to engage with
this way this pedagogy said two years
ago by dengue experts and so my
contributions is it going to be very
very different than the last photograph
we function as a sensor so we need food
bank and we lost says student enrollment
so how do we get to give feedback
well most of it from a computer cccc is
fun candice is designed to help students
change or improve their behavior
behavior never to personalize this is
one of the key key assumptions of giving
constructive feedback and sorrow sorrow
sorrow
our case we have what's referred to us
mid-block assessment to our parishioners
developing into into block so you know
cardiovascular block pulmonary block
where students in a focus on a
particular set by the system and he's
black cross between five to six to six
weeks and sorry about and and and the
storm groups Exchange building blocks
and so sorry no particular state and
local
will stand
interact with that particular group of
students on you for that period of five
or six weeks and so that kids in our
suite 6 web stuff they sort of unique
room unless we have what's good luck
assessment while showing you turn my
students are just very busy I'm very
busy doesn't think much in five minutes
seven minutes and we talked and you know
we talked about how things are going and
I tell they're still and you know what I
think about his or her participation
process so far and they tell me what
they think about my
contribution says as a as a as a tutor
so we have a very brief conversation but
he's not concerned you know if there's
something there was a problem with the
students or whatever reason is not
contributing their way you know that
expected to this is the time are often
actually it's an earlier than that this
is the time when you really lead to that
student know that you have consented
that they have to and that they have to
change they have to change and they have
to improve their contributions
sirens again going back to the
importance of addressing behaviour
rather than personality so you know I
noticed we've talked about instead of
you seen shy right where you make an
assumption about the personality of that
person and then I wouldn't say that I
noticed that you doing talk to a in
front of the group you know if I'm
really concerned that the predicted that
the student hasn't contributed much then
I would ask the student do either meet
with me today to tell you are signed
sometime during the
day you know when we could meet for a
few minutes and shot so they knock 222
characteristics of good feedback to feel
like I should be specific rather than
general you know you want to know when
you provide feedback and wants to
address a specific issue rather than
then be ambiguous and then of course
size from that should include both
positive and constructive compromise
instead of starting with with your
concerns you want to start with an hour
talking about a bad defends the decision
was doing well okay and then make a
transition to be a concern as far as
this is concerned Duncan being dramatic
are some things and and she in our case
we do students as a sign that the
suspect that day and they they get a
written assessment of their
contributions it did they get a copy and
then a second copy goes to the dean's
office and so it's it's it's it's it's
too bad that I she's including the final
but I think this point is very important
what he was doing this with you in an
hour in our assessment respiration
participation professional behavior
professionals must do to access content
knowledge
in computers and actually see you know
it was started
introduced in our curriculum our way
back to my son and I think the
first-year students are sure where r us
on their knowledge I'm running back
happening was that students were
complaining you know 25 percent of
brownie points from the from the
trumpeter ever ever stilleto wanted to
convince them that they allow despite
this they know the most and of course
that's completely ruined it was about
the process of people notice about Sharm
I took us my plan let's say again is
something that we want to we want to
have a previous commitment includes
unlimited number of lectures and provide
sufficient time for self-directed less
time and made earlier this is always a
bit of a headache special ceremony
stated you know how do we find time
another equipped for this process to
happen but you talked to those questions
if you really are serious about
introducing introducing P anyway he can
be
of the
diversity is going to be at the level of
the college level of the department
audit committee they love their own
course that means to again make sure
that there's time in that curriculum for
students to properly engage in all
phases of so yes is not dominate again
just this concept is very very difficult
for most of us to accept because we love
him of course I was convinced that what
we teach 16 president and it has to be
treading into correctly but if you issue
we're really serious about this
severe incidents should have them back
and they say
when I was engaged in this in this
exercise video sit there and again I was
very very rare upset the beginning
because this business because I'm a
sanction abuse of process was anything
everything that i think is important it
has to be part of my left chest to be no
problem I session and then I realized
after the actual spending some time to
think about it I realized admits that
she thinks that I'm not that's
critically important there things that
I'm not too is that my son is really
dumb has to know if you have one going
to be very good doctors say say say
hwang there has to be put on that it
created forests of the russian space
it's a nice sense of component of this
is a
PDF program in a job she recently and
because they they asked me to comment
and and and comment on few on she
respects outside of their people
curriculum and it was one of those cases
where you know still on the mountain
village in Kenya
to me some administrators were very
frustrated live Rugby customers do not
have time to engage in this process you
know they'll as I give you a good
example that you know it's not going
through very well as his students are
going to step into the TV at eleven
o'clock at night and exhausted but that
was when the case in that in the medical
school that I visited you know I'm so
sad that there's a ride home I keep calm
and patience you know change this review
another and I'm going to ask because i
three Hashem minutes for further
discussion and you know we do something
with your life
need to go back to talk talk about that
a bit more pleased to see this out but
just let me summarize does does this
they're very then slept understanding
I'll cover the lots and lots of topics
and you know but again I thought I hope
I R Us and managed to convey the message
that we are talking about so complex and
so and so it's very difficult to talk
about people and try two minutes and
then so so it's a few dozen leads to
talk about their size then I
mother happy to to engage in this sense
871 side of some house dance and do so
so so danse absolutely no direct
instruction so there's not another thing
that actually we're winning surprised me
when I this is it that that medical
school shootings ago was that students
actually we're giving lectures during
ppl to tell us which is something I've
never seen ever going to steal against
expectation was that the students had to
begin with cover one of those loan
issues that I that I thought we talked
about earlier than they would come back
and even without giving lecture on the
topic then they that they can't do it
again this this this this missed
opportunity this is based upon it's not
about you know about students giving
lectures it's about providing students
with the opportunity to really engage in
a meaningful conversation about things
that they've learned on their own it's
again what about you know it's not a lot
of time
showing the rest of the world how small
people aren't so bad for Nancy you know
deep conversation about about the issues
that relate to the case and above issues
that the students are expected to
discuss some of its construction my
presentations and the assessment should
be focused assessment should not only
focus on Dec 02
declarative knowledge so it's all gone
you know because if you do this you may
run into problems that I mentioned in
just a few minutes ago in terms of deuce
well-run it's a student initiated
learning winning the Special Forces as a
as a facilitator is a tool if you are
going to develop two cases and you know
you never returning with alternate these
students once it's too bad but you know
what specifically they will learn where
they find this information how they're
going to approach it it's all going to
be initiated by and controlled by then
so so it's all about socialization and
professional behaviour rates affecting
again whether it's medicine engineering
education
emphasis on South studying this is again
a critically important aspect of this of
this process and destined for some
students independent learning and
collaborative professional
problem-solving skills and not again
on lectures so I think this brings us to
their grandparents home now so it's just
deadly she still ok if that is a long
story parallel room
legislated for a lot more slides so
let's let's let's talk about let's let's
let's let's I said this is this is a
very complex there is some areas there's
do air
typically have discussed this peace
process and we works in real life
attentive process so we're talking about
and they don't know about the process
and functions since there are five stops
with that
and each completion of each series of
steps Berserker asset to their desire to
go and so sad and stopped well I hope so
ok so substance other than just the case
then the data commercial aspect of the
PCC listed them as they define problems
they identify key key information then
had a then they they discuss been very
they come up with soap opera since they
they they attempt to describe on the
line mechanisms are full of information
that has been released and on at some
point they recognize the limits of
international audience of their
knowledge at some point you have a safe
room you the power to really
you know we need more to to be able to
solve this case I'm so so so this is ran
when they discuss weapons for missions
new there they requested more
information on this whole process is
repeated again ok and at some point in
our cases suzhou you maybe I'll and a
half hour from time two minutes into
into the detail then recognize they they
recognize the limits of their knowledge
you know there are some really you know
they they they they decide that they
cover everything that we're a better
there's really nothing more that they
can add to the conversation and this is
when they generate learning issues this
is when they generate there's are are
come out with various
you know issues that they need to cover
and and they then engaged in research
website maybe a lawsuit under south will
say China and South 720 said this is
this is this is the time when when they
work on their own they come back the
next day or two days shy of information
that means termination tractor parts of
the case and then we start you know then
they again we're getting summation and
then again generate passed a refined
hypothesis and this this process is
repeated and then you know into second
tutorial again at some point they're
going to say we don't know how to deal
with then we have nothing else to
contribute to this process generated
online your shoes and you know again
research and study on their own and you
know how and another case again by the
end of the tutor on Sunday which is the
last day of the week
you know they they did the case is this
is his cell so this is how this is how
it how it works at CBC and then you know
there are different ways of the pair of
approaching this this this this this
whole process
but but I hope that I that he was very
aware
briefs and come dance session I was able
to cover all the key key concepts of ppl
that I really need to be in place if we
really wanted to to cover what we do
what we implement this problem based on
our content your full attention and time
I'll be more than happy to answer your
questions